# Franklin Finger

33 Markfield Drive Charleston, SC 29407 <u>franklinfinger@yahoo.com</u> <u>www.linkedin.com/in/franklinfinger</u>

## **Operations Manager**

Creative and business-savvy **general manager and sales professional** with 14 years of progressive experience across a broad range of management functions and diverse industry segments. Proven ability to combine vision, creativity, organization and strong business acumen with well-developed operations and leadership qualities to support and implement goals for the organization, product launches, and branding-rebranding initiatives, positioning companies and products for success.

## Areas of Expertise

Strategic Business Planning Conflict and Dispute Resolution Customer Service Management Vender Relations Inventory Management Team Building and Training

Cell: 843-338-1020

# **Professional Experience**

Southern Eagle Distributing Charleston, South Carolina (2013- 2014)

#### Sales Representative

- Increased sales by 7 percent with relationship building and gaining new business
- Executed new product launches and promotions with 6 new products

Ben Arnold Beverage Company

Charleston, South Carolina (2012-2013)

### Sales Development Representative

- Selling display ideas and new products to key decision makers
- Serve as primary contact for Costco to position Ben Arnold as distributor of choice

Captain Woody's Bar and Grill

Hilton Head Island, South Carolina (2009-2012)

#### **General Manager**

- Responsible for payroll, inventory, schedules, accounting and all day-to-day operations
- Established new inventory system for retail items to maximize profits and increase sales by 20 percent

Ocean Grille Restaurant - Lowrey Group

Hilton Head Island, South Carolina (2007-2009)

#### **General Manager**

- Created an incentive program with local hotel managers which increased business 15 percent the first year and 25 percent the second year
- Developed monthly and yearly budgets then met or exceeded goals

## **Education**

University of South Carolina Columbia, SC Bachelor of Science in Hospitality, Retail, and Sports Management Major: Retail Management

December 2011

Dean's List Senior Year